

PROFILE

Starting from 2015 began proactively working on web related projects as a Full Stack Web developer.
Starting from middle of 2018 began proactively working on blockchain related projects as a Blockchain software engineer.

My experiences range from creating both front-end blockchain applications to backend architecture design and implementation, smart contract development, testing, auditing and development of dApps for Fintech, defi, and other industries that need the power of decentralization, tokenization, and smart contracts.

CONTACT

EMAIL:

onedream1214@outlook.com

CODE REPOSITORIES

https://github.com/devstar1992

WANG XIANXIU

Web & Blockchain Developer

EDUCATION

Wuhan University2011 - 2015
Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science

WORK EXPERIENCE

Blockchain Developer Jinghua Network

2018-2020

Worked as a blockchain developer to develop and manage Dapps, and DeFi platform.

Full Stack Developer Vanguard Software, co.ltd

2015-2017

- \cdot Worked alongside product managers to re-architect a multi-page web-app into a single page web-app built in React resulting in a yearly revenue lift of \$1.1M
- \cdot Built the logic for a streamlined ad-serving platform that scaled to our 10M users which improved page speed by 14% after implementation

SKILLS

